http://www.templejc.edu/about/privacy-notice/

Privacy Notice
HomeTemple College»About Us»Privacy Notice
Temple College is committed to ensuring the privacy of personal information. We do not actively share personal information gathered from our web servers. However, because Temple College is a public institution, some information collected from the Temple College website, including summary server log information, emails, and information collected from web-based forms, may be subject to release. This means that while we do not share or sell information unless solicited, in some cases we may be compelled by the Texas Open Records Act to release information.
Temple College complies with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which prohibits the release of education records without student permission.
The Temple College website contains links to external websites. The College is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of external web links.
Information We Gather
The following information may be collected and stored automatically from all users accessing the Temple College website to browse or download information:
Internet address of computer being used
Web pages requested
Referring web page
Date and time
Type of web browser being used
This information is used to occasionally create summary statistics that are used for purposes such as assessing what information is of most interest to users, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will not be released to outside (third) parties unless legally required.
Personal Information You Provide to Us
Temple College does not retain personally identifiable information about you when you visit its websites unless you choose to provide such information to us (i.e. sending an email, participating in a survey, responding to a request for information or “contact us” form, etc.). We consider any information that could reasonably be used to identify you as “personally identifying information.” This includes, but is not limited to:
name
address
email address
Social Security number
any combination of data that could be used to identify you such as your birth date, zip code, and gender.
If you provide personal information in an email or by completing a form and submitting it through our website, we may use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested. We do not collect personal information from such communications for any purpose other than to respond to you. We do not collect information for commercial marketing.
Security and Accuracy of Personal and Confidential Information
Although no computer system is 100 percent secure, Temple College has deployed extensive security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control.
If you are concerned about the accuracy of information contained in your personal records, you should refer to the appropriate custodian of record.
Off-Site Links
Links to Non-Temple College organizations are provided solely as a service to our users. These links do not constitute an endorsement of these organizations or their programs by Temple College, and none should be inferred. Temple College is not responsible for the content found at these links.
Temple College follows the State Website Linking and Privacy Policy posted on the Department of Information Resources (DIR) website.
